[CALOY] I'm ready.
I'm on my way to Billy's.
[RAIN] Is this true?
Caloy escaped!
[SPRAY PAINT HISSING]
- [BILLY GRUNTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- Stop it!
- Help!
Shut up-- [CALOY YELPS]
- [BILLY YELPS, GROANS]
- [CALOY GRUNTS]
My God, Billy!
Billy!
Billy?
Help! Please help us!
Billy? Billy!
My God, Billy, what happened?
Billy! Billy. Billy.
Help!
Please help us!
Billy? Billy, Billy, Billy.
My God!
Jordan!
Jordan, help me!
- Auntie Pres!
- Billy?
- What happened to Billy?
- Watch her for a second.
I'll call an ambulance.
Dude!
[CALOY] She fought back, so I beat her up.
I slammed her head against the wall.
[BEA] For heaven's sake, Caloy!
Why did you hurt her?
You were just supposed to spray-paint
their walls to scare her! That's it!
Why did you hurt her?
He hurt Billy?
Serves her right!
Come on, 'Bi…
You were detained.
You lost your job.
You've got a case against you.
And all of that happened because of Billy.
- Billy.
- Dude.
How do you feel?
What about Oliver?
And Auntie Pres? Where are they?
They're safe.
Dude, you scared the shit out of me.
Sorry.
When are they going to stop?
What they're doing to us
just keeps getting worse.
What matters is you're okay.
What if…?
I just don't know what I would do if…
I'm just glad you're okay.
[ENRICO] What happened here?
Someone broke in. The intruder
even spray-painted their walls.
How are the people who live here?
Where are they?
[NEIGHBOR]
Billy probably got hurt fighting back.
They took her to the hospital.
Nurse, which room is Benilda Cariño in?
Okay, sir. Hold on.
I'll check which room she's in.
Cariño…
- A cup of coffee, please.
- Okay.
Jordan, Billy is asleep.
The doctor gave her a painkiller.
Are you sure I don't need
to go back there, Auntie?
Yeah. I'll look after her for now.
[PHONE CHIMES]
I'VE BEEN TEXTING YOU FOR HOURS.
WHEN ARE WE MEETING UP AGAIN?
Are you free tomorrow?
SORRY, BRANDON. MAYBE NEXT TIME.
WE HAVE A FAMILY EMERGENCY.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Dad?
Billy? Sweetie?
["MAG-ISA NA LANG AKO"
BY SHANIAH ROLLO PLAYING]
Dad…
Are you leaving?
What time are you coming home?
I'll wait for you, Dad.
I'll miss you.
[SOBS]
["MAG-ISA NA LANG AKO" CONTINUES]
[BIRDS TWITTERING]
They're installing the last one.
They're almost done.
They also arrived on time.
Thanks for the recommendation.
Hopefully, with all the CCTV cameras
you had installed,
Caloy and Bea won't even
think of going back there.
Rightly so.
Charm, thank you.
I'll make it up to you tomorrow.
Okay, bye.
- Ma'am, it's done. Everything's installed.
- All done?
[BILLY] Okay, let me check it.
Okay. It's working now, sir.
- Thank you.
- [MAN] Okay.
- Here's your payment.
- Thank you.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hello? What's taking you
so long to respond?
So, can I see you tomorrow?
Brandon…
Brandon, I'm sorry.
I'm not available.
You always say that.
You're just making up
excuses at this point.
What? Have you changed your mind about me?
Don't be dramatic. It's not like that.
There's a lot going on at home,
so I don't have time to see you.
Brandon, we're going to eat,
so I'm hanging up. Bye.
He… Hello?
Hello?
[PHONE CHIMES]
YOU'RE ALWAYS CANCELING
- [BILLY] Auntie Pres?
- Yes?
- The CCTV cameras are done.
- Oh, okay.
Billy, I have something to give to you.
- One for you, one for me.
- Mm-hmm.
There you go.
This is how you use it.
- Remove this side.
- [BILLY] Mm-hmm.
- Aim at their eyes.
- Yes.
- Press it. Aim towards the bad guy.
- Copy.
I know how to use it, Auntie. Thank you.
- Okay. Here.
- Sorry for making you worried.
Hey, don't worry about it.
You're not a burden.
What bothers me is the people
who are pestering you.
They're the ones
who should apologize to me.
Always have that in your bag.
- Bring it with you. Okay?
- Yes, I promise.
All right, come on. Let's eat.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
[PRECIOUS] Fortunately,
I managed to get some stock.
Come on, let's eat.
Okay.
Do you want some fish?
- Okay, Auntie.
- I'll put it on your plate.
Hey.
Is your head aching again?
No, Auntie Pres.
I just remembered something
that was like a dream.
What was it?
[OLIVER] Auntie, Billy, look.
I learned something new.
- [WHOOSHES]
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
- This is called "jab, slip."
- [BILLY] Wow.
[OLIVER] I'm going to use it
when the thief comes back.
I'll knock him out.
Oh, no. No. Come, sit here.
I have something to tell you.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll be going to school with you.
I'll stay there and watch you.
I already filed for leave.
What?
Why?
Sir Eric is there
to defend me from bullies.
Besides, I can take on Biboy myself.
No, no. You can't change my mind.
I'll stay there and watch you, okay?
I can manage on my own, Auntie.
[PRECIOUS] Mm…
He's a big boy now.
I don't think he wants me
to accompany him, Billy.
Didn't he use to cry so much
whenever we took him to school?
Didn't he used to cling to my legs?
[FAKE SOBS]
[OLIVER] Well, it's different now.
- Hmm?
- [PRECIOUS] Hmph!
- You're still that baby, right?
- [PRECIOUS CHUCKLES]
- You're our baby.
- Baby.
- No! No!
- You're still a baby.
- Baby.
- Smells like a baby.
- No, no, no!
- You're our baby.
- Right?
- No!
- You're still a baby.
- I'm not a baby!
- Drink your water, baby.
- No!
The blotter and medico-legal report
of Carlos Toledo's assault
have been filed.
His records also include
vandalism on your property.
We will keep monitoring it.
Sir, what's the update on Bea Mercado?
Bea Mercado has been under surveillance
since last week.
I had some officers
go to their house for questioning.
You can count on us. Don't worry.
We will do our best.
You know, that's what you guys always say.
But nothing ever happens.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MOUTHS SOFTLY] Calm down.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello, Brandon.
I already told you yesterday.
I can't meet up with you.
It's not that I want
to end things between us,
but I really need to go with Oliver.
I'll be there in a bit.
You can leave Oliver alone for a moment.
Huh? Oh, I really can't.
I'm on my way.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh, Precious, excuse me,
and please don't be offended.
But it's okay, you can leave.
Since I'm here, I can look after Oliver.
Oh, you don't have to. It's okay.
Thank you, Sir Eric.
I'm surprised admin allowed you.
I heard parents and guardians
aren't allowed to wait here.
They allow exemptions,
especially in special cases.
Special case? Why?
What happened to Oliver?
Uh…
Nothing happened to Oliver.
Someone broke into our front yard
the other night.
We already reported it to the police.
But I'm worried whoever broke in
might come back,
so I'm watching him in school.
Come back? What? Why?
Oh, no reason.
I'm just not taking any chances.
Well, yes. As a parent,
you really feel more at ease
when your child is with you.
Have some refreshments.
Ma'am, sir.
I'll do it.
I'll tell the truth.
That Caloy guy…
He courted me before.
But I turned him down.
I mean, it's like he's obsessed with me.
I kept rejecting him,
but he remained persistent.
This is different
from your previous statement.
Why are you only saying this now?
Because
I'm scared of Caloy.
He's obsessed with me.
I thought he might hurt me
if I reported him and ratted him out.
Are you saying that
you have nothing to do with this?
Here.
What's this? Where is this?
I have no idea.
I had nothing to do with it.
Billy Cariño's house.
Billy's house?
He has actually lost it. Look, Ma.
- He's crazy.
- Oh, right.
He is. He's crazy.
Did he do anything to Billy?
He assaulted Ms. Cariño.
He hurt Billy?!
[BEA] That's insane.
See? I told you. He's obsessed with me.
How's Billy? Is she okay?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You know, sir, ma'am…
I feel like Caloy found out.
Caloy found out that I didn't like Billy.
So he did that.
He probably thought
I'd be happy with what he did.
I told you that he was obsessed with me.
He's charmed by my beauty.
So it's really scary.
Whenever he'd come here,
we never let him in.
Because I'm terrified
of what he might do to my Bea.
So, please help us.
Catch him and put him behind bars.
That's right, ma'am.
Also, we need protection.
Maybe you can give us a bodyguard too.
For our own safety.
A bodyguard?
The report claims
you might have instructed Toledo
to cause trouble at Billy Cariño's house.
[MARIELA] No…
Me?
I would never do that, ma'am!
Why would I?
Who even told you that?
You know what? Just prove it!
And if you do,
I'll take myself to the police station
and have myself locked up!
Believe me, I'll do that!
[BEA HUFFING]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Look, I still have to get ready for work.
Do you have any more questions?
No, that's all.
We'll just get back to you.
Goodbye.
[MARIELA] Thank you.
That Billy can go to hell.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh…
Ma. [CHUCKLES DRYLY]
Don't give it too much thought. [HUFFS]
It's nothing.
[SCOFFS]
I'll take care of it. Don't worry, okay?
Calm down, calm down.
[MUSIC SWELLING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[LOW ELECTRICAL HUM]
[MARIELA GROANS]
Damn it!
The power's gone!
Uh, Ma, don't worry. Okay?
I've already applied for work.
Once I'm hired,
I'll request an advance on my salary
so we can cover the rent and power bill.
Don't worry, Ma.
Everything is going to be fine.
No.
We won't have any peace
until that Billy leaves us alone!
I'm sure she's behind the cops showing up!
Sure, but let it go.
She'll stop eventually.
When?
When you're locked up?
- Look, if you want--
- [KNIFE THUDS]
[BEA] Uh, Ma…
What I want
is for you to let me deal with Billy.
I'll handle her, okay?
Ma, listen. I can do that.
Ma, look at me.
Look at me, Ma. Swear to me.
Ma, promise me this. Okay?
Billy is mine. Leave her to me, okay?
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay?
Ma?
- That's a promise, okay?
- Mmm.
Okay, I'll leave now.
Bye, Ma.
[MUSIC BUILDING UP]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC STING]
They have to pay for what they did.
Before they do anything else.
I just realized
how important she is to me.
Wish me luck actually
falling asleep tonight.
- Do you want me to go there?
- Huh?
I'm back to square one.
That should've been mine,
but Billy just had to steal it!
Just use me.
I'll get back at Billy.
[MARIELA] That Billy can't
look down on you now!
Is there really no way we can look
at Mariela Mercado's files?
Bea has a huge grudge against you.
I hope we finally learn why.
My family's safety is at stake here.
I don't know why she hates Billy so much,
to the point that she even
conspired with a criminal.
A criminal?
[BILLY] A woman has been standing
outside for a while now.
I can't make her out clearly.
- I'll check it out.
- No, you won't!
Ma?
[MARIELA] I can't bear to
see you suffer, my dear.